Raymond Gakwaya

I'm an experienced Software Engineer with verifiable success leading teams in delivering appropriate technology solutions for desktop and mobile products. Comprehensive knowledge of platform development, enterprise architecture, agile methodologies, cloud services, and web-based applications. Innovative change agent with a unique mix of high-level technology direction and deep technical expertise.

KN 12 Avenue, Muhima Kigali City, (250) 789932381 raymond42.gr@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

Andela, Kigali-Rwanda— Full-Stack Software Engineer

July 2019 - April 2020

Andela provides companies with access to the top 1% of global tech talent. They identify high-potential developers on the African continent, shape them into world-class technical leaders, and pair them with companies as full-time, distributed team members.

Andela developers work as full-time engineers with companies ranging from the Fortune 500 to high-growth startups.

LifeStores HealthCare , Lagos-Nigeria — *Backend Software Engineer*

Nov 2019 - Feb 2020

Lifestores Healthcare aims to be the leading pharmaceutical retail company for the Nigerian mass market. I was working in a remote agile team development to build a pharmaceutical software called HealthId.

TIGO, Kigali-Rwanda — Sales & Marketing officer

2017 - 2018

Tigo which now emerged with Airtel, offers phone services like – prepaid, postpaid, mobile internet, broadband. I worked there as an internet broadband sales & marketing officer.

PROJECTS

Authors Haven — Full-stack Developer, DevOps

Authors Haven was an Andelan project which was for creating a community of like minded authors to foster inspiration and innovation by leveraging the modern web. I worked as a full-stack developer and also DevOps of this project.

Stack: PREN(Postgres, React, Express, Node js)

Converge - Backend Developer

Converge is an Andela internal product that manages the availability and use of Andela meeting rooms.

Stack: Python/Flask

HealthID- Backend Developer

HealthID is an Inventory Management and Customer Engagement software platform designed for Pharmacists/Chemists and their Customers.

Stack: Python/Django

EDUCATION

OpenClassrooms, Paris – France — *Software Development Certificates*

July2018 - Feb 2019

OpenClassrooms is an online platform offering top quality, education-to-employment programs and career coaching services for students worldwide. I obtained six certificates in software development.

OTHER CERTIFICATES

Andela Bootcamp Certificate. This is a technical workshop that qualifies a person with skills in web development and in soft skills with EPIC values(Excellence, Passion, Integrity, and Collaboration).

Leadership Skills Certificate. December 2014, I obtained a certificate in leadership skills from Youth Impact Mission (YIM) conference, a students' conference held at King David Academy Kanombe

Video Production and Photography Certificate.

I obtained a certificate in photography and video production from Kigali International Art College

SKILLS

- NodeJs
- React
- React native
- Python
- Django
- Flask
- GraphQL
- SQL
- Docker
- AWS
- DevOps

LANGUAGES

English, Kinyarwanda

REFEREES

Joshua TAHINDUKA

Team Skills Learning Facilitator, Andela Rwanda <u>joshua.tahinduka@andela.com</u>

Tel: +250788663464

Bernard DUSHIMIMANA

Technical Manager, Andela Rwanda <u>bernard.dushimimana@andela.com</u>

Tel: +250782769303